<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Eddie Knight</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Eddie Knight</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Reserve ALL the rights! 2023</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eddieknight.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Pythonista’s Guide to the OWASP Top 10</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/04/14/python-owasp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/04/14/python-owasp/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re like many developers or IT professionals, you may have mixed feelings about these lists. I get it. On one hand, you know they&amp;rsquo;re important for keeping your applications and systems secure. On the other hand, they can be overwhelming, dry, and difficult to implement.
But what if I told you that security checklists don&amp;rsquo;t have to be that way? What if I showed you how to approach these lists in a whole new light, and make easy work of the items on them?</description></item><item><title>Conference Speaker: Devnexus 2023</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/04/06/devnexus-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/04/06/devnexus-2023/</guid><description>Atlanta, GA hosted 2023&amp;rsquo;s largest Java Conference in the United States.</description></item><item><title>5 Tools to Automate SBOM Creation</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/02/13/sbom-creation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/02/13/sbom-creation/</guid><description>If you search for “How to Automate SBOM Creation” you’ll find a huge number of results. As a software engineer, I personally get frustrated by those results almost instantly. Instead of telling me how to automate the creation of my SBOM, most of them spend half the article telling me why I should automate my SBOM creation.
I want to do this a bit differently by focusing just on tools you can actually use in your CI pipeline for free right now.</description></item><item><title>Open Source in Finance 101</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/02/08/devnexus-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/02/08/devnexus-2023/</guid><description>Grizz from FINOS interviews Eddie Knight and Colin Griffin on the fundamentals of Open Source in the Financial Services sector.</description></item><item><title>Stop the Low-Quality Contribution Plague</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2022/10/20/contribution-plague/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2022/10/20/contribution-plague/</guid><description>I was in a discussion thread with folks from Cloud Native Computing Foundation and Kubernetes today, and this phrase came up again. The context was something along the lines of… “we’re afraid that will encourage low-quality contributions.”
Let’s dig in to this.
Read More</description></item><item><title>What the OpenSSL Vulnerabilities Are…and Aren't</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2022/10/20/oss-contributor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2022/10/20/oss-contributor/</guid><description>In this article, we won’t be going into detail about how the vulnerability came to be or even how to patch it (in short: upgrade to the latest). Instead, we’ll be taking a quick look at what an exploit against these two new issues could be able to do- and compare it to two other common dependency exploits.
Read More</description></item><item><title>How to Become a New Open Source Contributor</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2022/09/22/oss-contributor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2022/09/22/oss-contributor/</guid><description>Becoming a new contributor to open source software is one of the biggest obstacles I watch people hit regularly.
I’ve seen a hundred false starts from recent grads and even people who have been working in tech for years. The obstacle is consistent, but the solution isn’t always simple.
Read More</description></item><item><title>Techstrong TV at Open Source Summit Europe 2022</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2022/09/22/techstrong-tv/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2022/09/22/techstrong-tv/</guid><description>Interview with Mike Vizard about deploying software to highly regulated environments.</description></item><item><title>Compliant Financial Infrastructure &amp; Eddie Knight</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2022/04/01/finos-cfi-interview/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2022/04/01/finos-cfi-interview/</guid><description>Interview with James McLeod about the Compliant Financial Infrastructure project and Eddie Knight&amp;rsquo;s career to date.</description></item><item><title>Recognition of Contribution: FINOS</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2021/01/06/devnexus-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2021/01/06/devnexus-2023/</guid><description>Eddie Knight and Lee Faus (GitLab Field CTO) recieved a Community Spotlight for their collaboration to push forward the Compliant Financial Infrastructure project.</description></item></channel></rss>