<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>event on Eddie Knight</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/tags/event/</link><description>Recent content in event on Eddie Knight</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Reserve ALL the rights! 2023</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eddieknight.dev/tags/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DevOpsDays Chicago 2023</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/08/10/devopsdays-chicago-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/08/10/devopsdays-chicago-2023/</guid><description>In 2023, the demand for secure software development skills is at an all-time high. As DevOps professionals, we need to focus on secure CI/CD pipelines, helping developers secure code, and securing supply chains.
During this workshop we’ll discuss best practices to lock down CI pipelines and how to find vulnerabilities in our dependencies. The OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities have remained the same for a long time, indicating that there’s still a lot of work to be done.</description></item><item><title>KCDC: All your Security Shifted to the Left</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/06/21/kcdc-workshop/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/06/21/kcdc-workshop/</guid><description>In this half-day workshop: We look at how to implement secure coding practices, and then move on to discuss the ins and outs of modern continuous integration. After we lock down our CI pipelines, we’ll look at how to find vulnerabilities in our dependencies. Armed with that information we’ll learn how to properly triage threats, exploits, vulnerabilities that affect our software, and how to streamline code improvements. Before we’re done, we’ll investigate modern processes for continuous deployment, including secure infrastructure as code development and how to lock down our CD pipelines.</description></item><item><title>Creative, Inclusive, and Sustainable Cybersecurity</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/05/10/openssf-panelist/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/05/10/openssf-panelist/</guid><description>Panelist at OpenSSF Day during Open Source Summit North America.</description></item><item><title>How I Got Involved with the OpenSSF</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/05/04/openssf-involvement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/05/04/openssf-involvement/</guid><description>Let’s get it out of the way early: it’s not always clear how you can best plug into organizations like OpenSSF. That’s why I’m writing this guest blog post as an “outsider.” I’m just your average tech employee who has become progressively more involved since my company, Sonatype, became members of OpenSSF.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Native Security Slam</title><link>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/04/18/cncf-slam/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eddieknight.dev/post/2023/04/18/cncf-slam/</guid><description>Organizer and host of this annual event. The topic was recently announced for 2023.
Security Slam is a 30-day challenge designed to help creators and users of CNCF projects improve their software supply chain security at scale. Participants will have access to the Security Slam Library, which will include articles and videos created by Sonatype to help improve security posture. Success metrics and participation awards will be announced at the kickoff webinar, so be sure to sign up and join us for this exciting event!</description></item></channel></rss>